Well, James Tallarico ain't it neither.
He took money from Zio billionaire Miriam Adelson.
This is Miriam Adelson.
And now I met Alan Dersovich, and he said the legal thing about four more years.
And I said, Alan, I agree with you.
So we can do it.
She said, think about it.
I'll give you another $250.
I will give you.
When he was asked about this, very point blank, he completely dodged the question and did not say, I will not take money from this person.
There's a theologian who said, I screamed at God for the starving children until I realized the starving children was God screaming at me.
And God is screaming at all of us in Gaza as we speak.
Israel has a right to exist and a right to defend itself just like any nation.
But Benjamin Netanyahu doesn't have the right to wage war against civilians, to use famine and collective punishment as tactics.
So to answer your question, as a U.S.
Senator, I will use the financial and diplomatic leverage in this country to stop the atrocities and the suffering in Gaza.
It's also for the people of Israel, because Benjamin Netanyahu's disastrous war has made the people of Israel and Jewish people all over the world less safe as a result.
And to answer your last question, no, I will not be accepting money from APAC in this race.
So, Texas, you know, you got two folks that are willing to sell you out and you should know that because you should make it so that neither of them are able to run because they will not have any support.
Because all these politicians, all these politicians care about is winning.
So if you made it clear to them that they better put up some better options, then they would because they can't win if you don't vote.